(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-25T23:26:07.094388",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: Notice to Visitors]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will be starting soon.]
Attention ご来場のお客様へ
[Attention: To All Visitors]
開演までしばらくお待ちください
[The concert will be starting soon.]
Sponsor 協賛
[Sponsor]
あ、こっちこっち！
Ah, over here, over here!
今日、２人じゃないんすね
You're not by yourselves today?
え？２人...
Huh? Two...
さっきの... ここで出会った人たち
The ones from earlier... people we met here.
え？
Huh?
心で君を抱きしめる
I hold you in my heart...
Joyに行こうぜ！
Let's go with Joy!
JOYSOUND X1
holoplus 大神ミオジャックしてみた！
[holoplus: Tried taking over as Ookami Mio!]
ご来場のお客様へ
[Notice to All Attendees]
二次販売グッズ
[Second Round Merchandise Sales]
本日は、大神ミオ 1st Live『Our Sparkle』にご来場いただき、ありがとうございます！
Thank you for coming to Ookami Mio 1st Live "Our Sparkle" today!
ウチウチ！ウチだよー！大神ミオだよー！
It's me, it's me! It's Ookami Mio!
わあ、みんな元気だぁ！
Wow, everyone's so full of energy!
最後までライブを楽しんでいただくために、いくつかご案内させていただきます。
To help you enjoy the concert to the very end, I have a few announcements to make.
元気いいネー！
So energetic!
公演中の撮影、録音、録画機材の使用は固くお断りいたします。
Photography, audio recording, and video recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
万が一、具合が悪くなってしまった場合は、無理をせず近くのスタッフへお知らせください。
If you happen to feel unwell, please don't push yourself and inform a nearby staff member.
会場内でのモッシュ、ダイブ、大きく飛び跳ねる、
Moshing, diving, jumping high into the air,
ステージにものを投げ込むなど、他のみんなの迷惑になったり、公演を妨げる行為は一切禁止です。
throwing objects onto the stage, or any other behavior that causes trouble or disrupts the show is strictly prohibited.
ルールを守って盛り上がってくださいね！
Please follow the rules and enjoy the show!
守っていただけない場合は、ご退場いただく可能性もあるので気をつけてね！
If you don't follow them, you may be asked to leave, so please be careful!
また、本公演は映像配信および写真撮影用のカメラが会場内に入り、客席が映り込む場合がございます。
Additionally, please note that cameras for live streaming and photography are present in the venue, and audience members may appear on screen.
これらの映像や写真はプロモーションなどに使用される可能性がございますので、予めご了承ください。
Please be aware in advance that these videos and photos may be used for promotional purposes.
みんなイイ子だねぇ！
You're all such good kids!
あ！ライブのハッシュタグは #ミオスパークル です！
Ah! The live hashtag is #MioSparkle!
ハッシュタグを使ってたくさん盛り上げてね！
Use the hashtag to hype things up!
それでは、開演までもう少しです！
Now then, there's just a little bit left until the show starts!
みんなで一緒に盛り上がっていこう！
Let's all get excited together!
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
ミオのコンサート
Mio's concert
（大好き！ 大好き！ 大好き！）
(We love you! We love you! We love you!)
そろそろ お時間ね
It's almost time, almost time
今日もいっぱい笑っていこう
Let's laugh a lot today as well
もうすぐ始まるよ
It's starting very soon
OUR SPARKLE Ookami Mio 1st Live.
[OUR SPARKLE - Ookami Mio 1st Live.]
しじまに響くような My Heart
My heart resonating through the silence...
大神ミオ ソロライブ 始まるよー！
Ookami Mio's Solo Live begins now!
とうとうと流れてく風景
The scenery flows steadily past,
刹那的な日々の中で
Amidst these transient days.
差し伸べられた手は優しく
The hand reached out to me was gentle,
鼓動に滴る ルビー熱の予感
A ruby dripping into my pulse, a foreboding of heat.
風に吹かれる
Blown by the wind,
そう生きてきたから
That is how I have lived.
君に会って気づく
Meeting you made me realize...
もう一人じゃない
I am not alone anymore!
射光 瞬きは声
Flashing light, blinking like voices,
描き続け響く
Resonating as we keep drawing forward.
爪弾く道 漆黒の胸
Plucking the path in this pitch-black heart,
ともに駆けてく夜
A night we dash through together.
遠く電波する思いは
Feelings transmitted from afar,
心燃やす情熱
A passion burning in my heart.
世界はいいんだよ
The world is fine as it is,
後ろに君がいるから
Because you are behind me.
私は迷わない
I will not hesitate,
光差す道へ
Towards the light-filled path!
無力だから 仲間を求め
Being powerless, I sought companions;
凍えるから 火を灯して
Freezing, I lit a fire.
変化とともに 進化していく
Evolving along with the changes,
この顛末は 誰も知らない
No one knows how this story ends.
君を信じる
I believe in you;
そう決めているから
That's what I've decided,
どんな非情も
So no matter how cruel it gets,
乗り越えられるよ
I can overcome it!
月光 この闇に唯一
Moonlight, the sole flower
凛と咲く花
Blooming bravely in this darkness.
恐れなのか 憧れなのか
Is it fear or longing?
向かい合う夜空
Facing the night sky,
未知を駆け抜ける私と
Running through the unknown, you and I
君が作り出す
Create together
この物語
This story.
単純な未来じゃない
It's no simple future;
湧き立つ情熱
Let's carry this surging passion
この声に乗せよう
Upon this voice!
空飛ぶ羽はなくても
Even without wings to fly,
手は繋げられたから
Because we were able to hold hands,
この運命を選んだ
I chose this destiny.
連鎖する遠吠えは
Chaining howls
しじまに響いて
Echo through the silence,
何度も何度も
Time and time again,
その絆を確かめ合った
Reaffirming that bond between us.
夜の静寂は 越え行く気配
The signs of passing through the night's silence,
月へ響く 爪弾く路
Resonating to the moon along this plucked path.
金狼の群れ 共になげく夜
A night where the pack of golden wolves laments together.
慟哭 伝播する思いは 心強くする
Wailing, these spreading feelings make my heart stronger.
共に行こうよ 隣に君がいるから
Let's go together, because you are by my side.
私は迷わない 光射す道へ
I will not hesitate on the path toward the light.
Listen to my howling...
狼が止まることはない
The wolf will never stop.
まだまだ走るよ！
We're still gonna keep running!
みんな ついてきて！
Everyone, follow me!
どこまで行こうか ネイビーの夜空に
How far shall we go into the navy night sky,
映る昨日の自分
Reflecting who I was yesterday?
夢見がちだった ベビーフェイスにさようなら
Goodbye to the dream-prone baby face.
見たくないもの照らす ハイビームに走る衝動
Impulses rushing under high beams that illuminate things I don't want to see.
跳ね除けて前へ行けば 信号は皆 色を失くし消えた
Pushing past them to move forward, the traffic lights all lost their color and vanished.
確かめたい 未知が続く慰めを
I want to feel the comfort of an unknown path stretching ahead.
深く深く濃くなる 夜を揺らす
Shaking the night that grows deeper, darker, and thicker,
微かな速度の光さえ 越えて行けるほどに
Enough to surpass even the faint speed of light.
強く強く踏み込んで
Stepping down hard, with all my strength,
僕は駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
I dash straight ahead,
譲れない思いを抱いて
Holding onto feelings I cannot yield.
標識だらけの街を抜け出して 明日を探してた
Escaping the signpost-riddled town, I searched for tomorrow,
常識の波に全部雑多と溶かしてた
Melting everything cluttering into the waves of common sense.
どこまで行けるのなんて 聞き合ったセリフ
"How far can we go?"—the line we kept asking each other,
吐いて 曇った窓ガラスに描いた本音
Breathing onto the fogged window pane and writing our true feelings,
すぐに指で消した
Only to erase them quickly with a finger.
臆病でも
Even if I'm faint-hearted...
揺るぎない軌跡 確かめた願いを胸に 遥か遠く
With an unshakeable locus and confirmed wishes in my heart, far into the distance,
軋むように軋んでも この灯火を灯し続け
Even if it creaks and groans, I'll keep lighting this flame,
ただ一つ答えを追いかけて
Chasing after a single answer.
脆くてもいい この腕で掴むために
It's fine to be fragile, as long as I can grasp it with these arms,
手を伸ばすよ 内鳴らす鼓動の限り
I reach out my hand for as long as my heartbeat thumps inside.
この道で迷って 見失って どこへ行くの
Getting lost on this path, losing my way, where am I heading?
目指す場所 その意味も ひとつしかないのに
Even though there's only one destination and one meaning to it all.
曇った視界は 夜に溶けても もう一度開けて行く
Even if my clouded vision dissolves into the night, it will clear up once again.
視線の先 僕を連れて行くよ きっと
Where my gaze leads, it will surely take me there.
みんな！行くよー！
Everyone! Here we go!
深く深く濃くなる 息を吸って 今加速を
Taking a deep, deep breath, accelerating right now,
傷つくほどに強く成ろう
Let's grow strong enough to endure the pain.
確かめたい色 動き出す 纏っている その体で
With that body clad in colors I want to confirm, starting to move,
鮮やかな夜空の果てへ
Heading toward the edges of the vivid night sky,
忘れないように
So I never forget.
深く深く濃くなれ 今を生きる この加速の
Growing deeper, deeper, and darker, living in the present of this acceleration,
光だって超えて行ける場所へ
To a place that can surpass even the light itself.
強く強く踏み込んで
Stepping down hard, with all my strength,
僕を駆ける ただ真っ直ぐに
Running straight ahead through my own path,
譲れない思いを抱いて
Holding onto feelings I cannot yield.
想いを抱いて 止まらないで
Holding onto my feelings, don't stop,
走り続ける意味を知るから
because I know the meaning of continuing to run.
きっと未来は色に溢れ
Surely the future will overflow with color,
まだ見ぬ世界をカラフルに染める
painting the unseen world in vivid hues.
もっと自由になりたいから
Because I want to be even more free,
ずっと ずっと ずっと 夢見てるの
I've been dreaming forever, forever, forever.
空に光る星のように 輝きたいと願う夜
On nights when I wish to shine like a star glowing in the sky,
広い世界に存在を証明したくて
wanting to prove my existence to this vast world...
出来ないことばかり数えても 胸が苦しくなるだけでしょ
Even if I only count what I can't do, it'll only make my heart ache.
私だって絶対 あの日の夢の続きになれるはず
Even I can surely become the continuation of that day's dream.
響く音色の中ほら 未知なる景色
Look, amidst the echoing melody lies an unknown landscape.
どこか感じてたのに 近づいた気がしたんだ
Though I felt it somewhere, I felt like I've gotten closer.
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先 描いた理想が想像を超える
Beyond this hand gently reached out, the ideal I drew exceeds imagination.
やっと見つける私の色 ずっと ずっと ずっと 追いかけるの
Finally finding my color, I'll chase after it forever, forever, forever.
限りないことを思い描いた 瞳に映るすべて
Everything reflected in my eyes, envisioning endless possibilities,
変わりゆく世界のリズム乗って モノクロ染めてゆく
riding the rhythm of a changing world, dyeing monochrome into color.
閉じ込めなくてもいいの 不安感じても 私だけの色で描こう
It's okay not to lock it away; even if I feel anxious, I'll paint with my own color.
きっと未来は色に溢れ まだ見ぬ世界はカラフルに染まる
Surely the future will overflow with color, painting the unseen world in vivid hues.
もっと自由に羽ばたくから ずっと あの日感じたままに
Because I'll spread my wings more freely, staying true to what I felt that day.
そっと伸ばしたこの手の先 描いた理想が想像を超える
Beyond this hand gently reached out, the ideal I drew exceeds imagination.
やっと見つけた私の色 ずっと ずっと ずっと 描いてくの
Finally found my color, I'll keep drawing it forever, forever, forever.
ありがとー！
Thank you!
はい！というわけで...
Alright! So then...
まずは自己紹介からしたいと思いますけど...
First off, I'd like to do my introduction, but...
みんな、分かってる人と分かってない人いるかもしれないから、一応説明するんですが...
Some of you might know, and some might not, so I'll explain just in case...
「うち、うち、うちだよー」って言ったら、みんな「大神ミオだよー」って言ってもらえたら、うちの自己紹介が完成するので...
When I say "It's me, me, me~!", if everyone responds with "It's Ookami Mio~!", my introduction will be complete...
言ってもらってもいいですかー？
So could you all say it for me?
それじゃあ、行きますよー！
Alright then, here we go!
うち、うち、うちだよー！
It's me, me, me~!
大神ミオだよー！
It's Ookami Mio~!
わぁー！本日はおおかみみおのソロライブ開催おめでとうございます！
Waaah! Congratulations on holding Ookami Mio's solo live concert today!
うちがおめでとうって言われる側だと思うんだけど、多分(笑)
Though I think I'm supposed to be the one receiving congratulations, probably (laughs).
すごいみんなー！
Everyone is amazing!
ソロライブの衣装、どうかなー？
How do you like my solo live outfit?
可愛いー？嬉しい！
Cute? I'm so happy!
なんと、なんと今回、あの...6年...と、まあ、もうちょっとで7年活動してきて... 尻尾が解放されてるんですー！
And guess what? This time, after... 6 years... well, almost 7 years of activity... my tails have been unlocked!
見て、見てー！
Look, look!
今までずっと...
Up until now, all this time...
ここの
Here on my...
足にね
leg, you see,
巻き付いていた
it was wrapped around...
尻尾がね
my tail, that is...
見えちゃった感じなんですけれど
It looks like it became visible, but...
嬉しいな なんか
I'm somehow happy about it!
ま、これはうちの自信の表れと言いますか
Well, this is an expression of my confidence, you could say.
自信がついたからこうやって尻尾が解放できたということで
Since I gained confidence, I was able to unleash my tail like this!
この舞台に
To this stage...
押し上げてくれたみんな、ありがとう！
Everyone who pushed me up to this stage, thank you!
ちょっと...
Phew...
汗かいてきちゃったかも...
I might have started sweating a bit...
ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much!
いやー ちょっとね 最初だし
Man... since it's still early on,
コール＆レスポンスとかしてみたけれど
I wanted to try doing a call-and-response, but...
どうかなー？
How about it?
ちょっとやってみようかな？
Shall I give it a try?
さっきね、オオカミミオにはなってもらったから
Earlier, I had you all act as "Ookami Mio",
んー どうしようかなー
Hmm, what should we do?
じゃあ、えっと
Then, well...
「オオカミミオ ソロライブ」って言ったら
When I say "Ookami Mio Solo Live",
みんな「アワースパークル！」って
everyone, could you say "OUR SPARKLE!"
大きい声で言ってもらってもいいですか？
in a loud voice?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
じゃあ行きますよ！
Alright, here we go!
オオカミミオ ソロライブ！
Ookami Mio Solo Live!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
すっごくよく聴こえる！
I can hear you so clearly!
ちょっとね、配信で見ている
For those watching on the stream,
そこ君も！
you over there too!
ツリー席の全員もよく見えてるよ！
I can see everyone in the tree seats clearly too!
コメントもありがとね！
Thanks for the comments, too!
いっぱい感心のね
Lots of my...
可愛い姿をスクショしてもらえたら嬉しいなって
cute poses, I'd be happy if you screenshot them...
思います！
...I think!
現地のみんなは一旦記憶にキャプチャーしてね
Everyone here in person, capture it in your memory for now, okay?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はい、そして
Yes, and...
#ミオスパークル で
using the hashtag #MioSparkle,
スクショや感想のポストもよろしくお願いします！
please post your screenshots and thoughts!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
いやさー
Man...
もうオオカミミオソロライブ
Ookami Mio Solo Live...
始まっちゃったらもうあっという間に
once it started, it felt like in an instant...
終わっちゃうのかと思うと
thinking that it'll be over so soon...
MCもまだまだ終わりたくないんだけど
I don't want the MC talk to end yet either, but...
もう始まった瞬間から終わる心配してるんだけど
I've been worrying about it ending from the moment it started!
今日はね
Today, you know,
たくさん最高にキラキラな
let's make lots of the most sparkling...
思い出作っていこうね！
...memories together!
はい、そして
Yes, and...
ちら見せ枠の皆さんには
to everyone watching the sneak peek...
残念なお知らせなんですけれど...
I have a sad announcement...
現地のみなさんはね、最後まで見れるのは確定なんですが
Everyone here in person is guaranteed to watch till the end, but...
無料配信は
the free stream...
ここでお別れとなります！
...will come to an end here!
というわけでね
So then,
ツリー席のチケットを買っていただければ
if you purchase a tree seat ticket,
続きが見れますので
you can watch the rest of the show!
ぜひぜひ買って頂ければなーって
So I'd be really glad if you bought one...
ミオファのみんなも思ってるよね！
Miofa fans think so too, right!
思ってまーす！
We think so!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you in advance!
「行かないでー！」
"Don't go!"
見て、おじーの...
Look, the old guys'...
「行かないでー！頂戴よー！」
"Don't go! Give it to us!"
イマジナリーミオファの声が聞こえてくるような...
It feels like I can hear imaginary Miofa voices...
騒がしいミオファの声ですね
What a noisy bunch of Miofa voices!
はい！というわけで
Alright! So then,
そろそろ次の曲行きますか！
shall we move on to the next song soon!
オオカミミオ ソロライブ
Ookami Mio Solo Live...
盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's get hyped up!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
[The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!]
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！